Up with People Archive 1937-2015 (bulk 1970-1990)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series VII: Photographic material, 1960-2010
  - Subseries 5: Photographic albums, 1969-1999
    - “Rhythm of the World” Publicity Photos, part 2, 1991-1993 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - “Rhythm of the World” Still Photography, part 1, 1991-1993 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - “Rhythm of the World” Still Photography, part 2, 1991-1993 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - “Roads” and “The Festival” Show Photographs, part 1, undated (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - “Roads” and “The Festival” Show Photographs, part 2, undated (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - “Roads” and “The Festival” Show Photographs, part 3, undated (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Various Slides and Photos I, part 1, undated (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Various Slides and Photos I, part 2, undated (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Various Slides and Photos II, part 1, undated (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Various Slides and Photos II, part 2, undated (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Various Slides and Photos III, part 1, undated (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Various Slides and Photos III, part 2, undated (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Various Slides and Photos IV, part 1, undated (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Various Slides and Photos IV, part 2, undated (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Various Slides and Photos IV, part 3, undated (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Various Slides and Photos V, part 1, undated (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Various Slides and Photos V, part 2, undated (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Various Slides and Photos V, part 3, undated (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Various Slides and Photos V, part 4, undated (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Various Slides and Photos VI, part 1, undated (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Various Slides and Photos VI, part 2, undated (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Various Slides and Photos VI, part 3, undated (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Various Slides and Photos VI, part 4, undated (Box 86, Folder 8-9)
    - Welcome to Denver, undated (Box 86, Folder 10)
- Series VIII: Oversize Material, 1965-1999
  This series contains oversize material from various series including Series II: Publications, Series III: Scores and Series VII: Photographs, Negatives and Slides.
  - Subseries 1: Posters, 1965-1990
    This series contains posters related to publicity and performances. It is arranged chronologically.
    - Colwell Brothers in Sing Out ‘65 Connecticut, 1965 August 7-8 (Box 87, Item 1)
    - Sing Out ‘66, Germany, 1966 (Box 87, Item 2)
    - Up with People, 1970 (Box 87, Item 3)
    - Up with People, Kanji Script, 1971 (Box 87, Item 4)
    - Up with People, Cast A, 1978-1979 (Box 87, Item 5)
    - Up with People, Cast B, 1972-1973 (Box 87, Item 6)
    - Up with People, Cast B, 1978-1979 (Box 87, Item 7)
    - Up with People, Cast C, 1978-1979 (Box 87, Item 8)
    - Up with People, Cast D, 1978-1979 (Box 87, Item 9)
    - Up with People, Cast E, 1978 (Box 87, Item 10)
    - A Half Time Salute, Super Bowl XIV, 1980 (Box 87, Item 11)
    - The Up with People Show Cast B European Tour, Signed, 1981 (Box 87, Item 12)
    - Up with People in Concert, Europe, 1983 (Box 87, Item 13)
    - Viva la Gente!, Rome, Italy, 1983 (Box 87, Item 14)
    - Vive les Gens, France, 1984 (Box 87, Item 15)
    - Silver Celebrations, Denver, 25th Anniversary, 1990 (Box 87, Item 16)
    - Up with People, with U.S.S.R. Cast Members, 1990 (Box 87, Item 17)
    - The Journey, 50th Anniversary show at Fox Tucson Theatre, 2015 (Box 87, Item 18)
    - Beat of the Future, undated (Box 87, Item 19)
    - Beat of the Future- Europe, undated (Box 87, Item 20)
    - Beat of the Future- Recruiting, undated (Box 87, Item 21)
    - Closing Ceremonies, Olympic Games, undated (Box 87, Item 22)
    - Saginaw Civic Center, Michigan, undated (Box 87, Item 23)
    - Show for all Seasons... For people of all ages, Up with People and Tucson Symphony, January 29; undated (Box 87, Item 24)
    - Up with People, undated (Box 87, Item 25)
    - Up with People, undated (Box 87, Item 26)
    - Up with People, undated (Box 87, Item 27)
    - Up with People, undated (Box 87, Item 28)
    - Up with People, undated (Box 87, Item 29)
    - Up with People, undated (Box 87, Item 30)
    - Up with People, undated (Box 87, Item 31)
    - Up with People, undated (Box 87, Item 32)
    - Up with People in Concert, undated (Box 87, Item 33)
    - Up with People in Concert, undated (Box 87, Item 34)
    - Up with People Presents Beat of the Future, undated (Box 87, Item 35)
    - Up with People Presents Time for the Music, undated (Box 87, Item 36)
    - Up with People Roads, undated (Box 87, Item 37)
    - The Up with People Show, undated (Box 87, Item 38)
    - The Up with People Show, undated (Box 87, Item 39)
    - The Up with People Show, German Language, undated (Box 87, Item 40)
    - The Up with People Show, German Language, undated (Box 87, Item 41)
    - Up with People, Super Bowls, Super Shows, Super Promotions, undated (Box 87, Item 42)
    - Up with People World in Motion, undated (Box 87, Item 43)
    - Viva la Gente!, undated (Box 87, Item 44)
    - Viva la Gente- El Mundo Entero Sobre El Escenario, Spanish Language, undated (Box 87, Item 45)
    - Viva la Gente!, Spanish Language, undated (Box 87, Item 46)
    - World Smart, Our Backpacks, undated (Box 87, Item 47)
    - World Smart, Our Campus, undated (Box 87, Item 48)
    - World Smart, Our Campus, undated (Box 87, Item 49)
    - World Smart, Our Classrooms, undated (Box 87, Item 50)
    - World Smart, Our Classrooms, undated (Box 87, Item 51)
    - World Smart, Our Classrooms, undated (Box 87, Item 52)
    - World Smart, Our Professors, undated (Box 87, Item 53)
    - World Smart, Our Textbooks, undated (Box 87, Item 54)
    - Sing Out Festival, Monaco, 1968 January 31 (Box 87, Tube 1)
    - The Up with People Show, undated (Box 87, Tube 2)
  - Subseries 2: Scores, 1970-1985
    This series contains scores used by Up with People. It is arranged alphabetically by title.
    - All we got is us, undated (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - The American Popular Song (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - The American Popular Song (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Back in Style Medley 2, undated (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Beat of the Future, undated (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Belgian Folk Dance, undated (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Been Waitin’, undated (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Bermuda Medley, undated (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Breakin’ New Ground, undated (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Canadian Pacific Medley, 1982 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Can we Sing a Song of Peace?, undated (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Carnival, undated (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Celebration, 1973 (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Chaser, 1985 (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Classical Medley, undated (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - Coming of Age, undated (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Dajčovo Horo, undated (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - A Day in April, undated (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Don’t Keep it, undated (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Eres Tú, 1973 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Ever Living Soul, 1973 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Everyday Heroes, undated (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Festa Humana, undated (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Fifties Prom, undated (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Fjäriln Vingad Syns På Haga, undated (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - The further we Reach Out, 1973 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Go for it all, undated (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Gopak, undated (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Global Medley, 1970-1971 (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Hometown to Pan Am, 1970 (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - If there is Love, undated (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - I’s the B’y, undated (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - It takes the Whole Village, undated (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Italian Medley, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - John David Sebastian Smith, undated (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Just People Brick by Brick, undated (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - LA, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - La Costilla, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - La Domenica, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - La Negra, 1983-1985 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Lanigan’s Ball, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - La Petite Gayole, undated (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - La Santa Espina, undated (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - LA song part one, undated (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Let the River Flow, undated (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Look for the People, undated (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Louisiana Folk, undated (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Merry Christmas to you all, undated (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Nunca, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - One Shot Deal, undated (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Overture, 1972 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Oxdans, undated (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Pays de Coeur, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - The Place I Come From, 1974-1975 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Pop Medley 20s, undated (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Pop Medley 30s, undated (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Pop Medley/Part One, undated (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Prelude, undated (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Raise a Ruckus Tonight, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Reunion, undated (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Roads final chorus, 1972-1973 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Room for Everyone, undated (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Rubens Cantate, undated (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Sixties Medley, 1982 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Skoczek Polka, undated (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Square Dance, 1972-1973 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Square Dance, 1974-1975 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Super Bowl Run-On, 1982 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Stand Together, undated (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Take the Cake, undated (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Thank You, undated (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - A Thousand Suns, undated (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Time to Take our Place, undated (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Traditional Medley, undated (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Together we can Find the Answers, undated (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - Ukrainian Dance, undated (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Uncle Victor and Auntie Ola, undated (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Un Giorno Di, undated (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Up with People, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Up with People, undated (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Up with People- Entre Acte, undated (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Up with People- Overture, 1980 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Up with People- Overture, undated (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Up with People- Reprises, 1972-1973 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Up with People- Reprises, 1985 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Up with People- Segue, 1983-1985 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Walk Lightly, undated (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Walk on Through (1 of 2), undated (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Walk on Through (2 of 2), undated (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Way Outside You, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - We’ll be There, undated (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - What Color is God’s Skin?, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Where Roads Come Together, undated (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Winter Medley, 1980 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - With Everything Changing, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 3: Photographs and Photo Albums, 1965-1982
    This series contains promotional albums and photographs from NFL Super Bowl events. It is arranged chronologically.
    - Promo Photo Album, 1965-1970 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Promo photo album, Various photos from the 1970s, Album 1, 1970-1979 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Promo photo album, Various photos from the 1970s, Album 2, 1970-1979 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Promo photo album, Various photos from the 1970s, Album 3, 1970-1979 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Super Bowl X, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Super Bowl XIV, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Super Bowl XVI, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 4: Scrapbooks, 1973-1999
    This series contains scrapbooks of international tours as well as news clippings. It is arranged chronologically.
    - CBS TV Special and Newspaper Clippings Scrapbook, 1973 April (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - North Andover, Massachusetts, 1976 May (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Various Newspaper Articles and Clippings, 1977 August-December (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Various Newspaper Articles and Clippings, September 1978-September 1979 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Japan, 1986 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Rome, Cast C (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Rome, Cast C (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 100, Folder 3)
- Series IX: Audio Visual Materials, 1962-2009
  This series is composed of audio visual materials. It contains performances, interviews and special appearances by Up with People. It is divided into three subseries.
  - Subseries 1: Record albums, 1962-1990
    This subseries contains professional recordings of Up with People music and performances as well as records of various people associated with Up with People such as the Colwell Brothers and Frank Fields. This subseries is arranged chronologically.
    - International Chorus of Moral Re-Armament- Songs of Oklahoma, 1962 (Box 101, Item 1)
    - Pace Magazine presents- Record #1, 1964-1965 (Box 101, Item 2)
    - Pace Magazine presents- Record #3, 1964-1965 (Box 101, Item 3)
    - Pace Magazine presents-Record #4, 1964-1965 (Box 101, Item 4)
    - Pace Magazine presents- Records #5, 1964-1965 (Box 101, Item 5)
    - Pace Magazine Presents- Record #6, 1964-1965 (Box 101, Item 6)
    - The Sing-Out Musical Up with People, 1965 (Box 101, Item 7)
    - Sing out Deutschland Ein Hoch Auf Die Menschen, 1967 (Box 101, Item 8)
    - Up with People- Frontiers of Tomorrow- Boy Scout Jamboree Album, 1969 (Box 101, Item 9)
    - Viva a gente!, 1969 (Box 101, Item 10)
    - Sing Out Suomi (Finnish), 1970 (Box 101, Item 11)
    - Reception at the White House for Governors, 1971 (Box 101, Item 12)
    - Up with People- Let All the People In, 1971 (Box 101, Item 13)
    - Up with People- Up With People!, 1972 (Box 101, Item 14)
    - Up with People!, 1972 (Box 101, Item 15)
    - The Up with People Show, 1972 (Box 101, Item 16)
    - The Best of Frank Fields, 1973 (Box 101, Item 17)
    - From Up With People: A Children’s Album Great Things, 1974 (Box 101, Item 18)
    - Up with People- Livin’ On, 1974 (Box 101, Item 19)
    - Up with People- The further we reach out, 1974 (Box 101, Item 20)
    - Up with People Sings: Get In Touch With America (Greyhound Corporation), 1974 (Box 101, Item 21)
    - The ‘75/’76 Show Album Up With People, 1975 (Box 101, Item 22)
    - Up with People- Self Title, 1977 (Box 101, Item 23)
    - Up with People- People are the Energy, 1979 (Box 101, Item 24)
    - Up with People- Times of Your Life (Eastman Kodak Company), 1979 (Box 101, Item 25)
    - Up with People- Encore!, 1981 (Box 101, Item 26)
    - Up with People- Super Bowl XVI, 1981 (Box 101, Item 27)
    - Up with People- Live in Concert, 1983 (Box 101, Item 28)
    - Up with People- “Beat of the Future”, 1985 (Box 101, Item 29)
    - Up with People- Time for the Music- The World Tour, 1987 (Box 101, Item 30)
    - Up with People- Face to Face- The World Tour, 1989 (Box 101, Item 31)
    - Up with People- 25th Anniversary Collection, 1990 (Box 101, Item 32)
    - Adelante Juventud (Caracas, Venezuela), undated (Box 102, Item 1)
    - The Cast of Up with People with Glen Close and Frank Fields- The World is Your Home/Colorado, undated (Box 102, Item 2)
    - The Colwells- How Much Do You Care?/Joan Of Arc, undated (Box 102, Item 3)
    - The Colwells- A New Tomorrow/Design for Dedication, undated (Box 102, Item 4)
    - The Colwell Brothers- No. 2, undated (Box 102, Item 5)
    - The Colwell Brothers- This is it!, undated (Box 102, Item 6)
    - The Crowning Experience, undated (Box 102, Item 7-8)
    - Give a Dog a Bone Songs from the Show, undated (Box 102, Item 9)
    - Linda Blackmore- Merry Christmas to you all, undated (Box 102, Item 10)
    - Live on Tour Up With People Featuring H.J. Chocktim Smithfields- Live in France, undated (Box 102, Item 11)
    - Songs from “The Crowning Experience”, undated (Box 102, Item 12)
    - Springbok Stampede Stormloop (South Africa Afrikaans), undated (Box 102, Item 13)
    - Up with People featuring Mary Dobbins, undated (Box 102, Item 14)
    - Up with People, undated (Box 102, Item 15)
    - Up with People! III, undated (Box 102, Item 16)
    - Up with People- Free Spirit, undated (Box 102, Item 17)
    - Up with People- Self Title, undated (Box 102, Item 18)
    - Up with People! Sing out Explosion, undated (Box 102, Item 19)
    - Up with People- Viva La Gente! Recorded in Italian, undated (Box 102, Item 20)
    - Up with People- ¡Viva La Gente!, undated (Box 102, Item 21)
    - Up with People Viva La Gente and Amics dels Classica Orquesta de Cambria, Mardid, Spain (2 en 1), undated (Box 102, Item 22)
    - Up with People- What Color Is God’s Skin?, undated (Box 102, Item 23)
    - The Up with People Sound- Frank Fields and Cabot Wade, undated (Box 102, Item 24)
    - The Up with People Sound- Glennie Close and Paul Colwell, undated (Box 102, Item 25)
    - The Up with People Sound- Steve Geil, undated (Box 102, Item 26)
    - The Up with People Sound- The Volunteers and The Colwell Brothers, undated (Box 102, Item 27)
    - Viva La Gente! Esplosione di Sing out (Italian), undated (Box 102, Item 28)
    - Viva La Gente! (Up With People) (Italian), undated (Box 102, Item 29)
    - Viva La Gente! Up With People in Latin America, undated (Box 102, Item 30)
  - Subseries 2: Audio, 1965-2009
    This subseries contains audio reels and tapes from Up with People events and performances. This series is arranged chronologically. Access copy CDs are available. The migrated copies of these audio visual materials were transferred from the originals in 2012 and 2013.
    - Sing Out ’65 Hollywood Bowl tape 1 of 4 (32 minutes), 1965 September 19; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 103, Item 1)
    - Sing Out ’65 Hollywood Bowl tape 2 of 4 (29 minutes), 1965 September 19; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 103, Item 2)
    - Sing Out ’65 Hollywood Bowl tape 3 of 4 (23 minutes), 1965 September 19; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 103, Item 3)
    - Sing Out ’65 Hollywood Bowl tape 4 of 4 (29 minutes), 1965 September 19; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 103, Item 4)
    - Frank Fields, Cast B Pace Records Reel 2 (21 minutes), 1967 January 31; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 103, Item 5)
    - UWP for Jack House, for air NBC-TV (Dated: July 28, 1968) (54 minutes), 1968 August 23; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 103, Item 6)
    - UWP LA Performance, Dec 11, 1968, Reel 1 of 2 (67 minutes), Audio tape reel to reel (Box 103, Item 7)
    - Christmas in the Stars (Instrumental & Vocal) Pace Publications (4 minutes), 1969 February 20; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 103, Item 8)
    - UWP LA Act I, Music Center Benefit (53 minutes), 1969; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 103, Item 9)
    - UWP LA Act II, Music Center Benefit (45 minutes), 1969; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 103, Item 10)
    - Live it Live, Live in London (22 minutes), 1970 July; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 103, Item 11)
    - Live it Live, Live in London (27 minutes), 1970 July; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 103, Item 12)
    - Rough unedited reel 1 (33 minutes), 1970 July 1; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 103, Item 13)
    - Rough unedited reel 2 (30 minutes), 1970 July 1; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 103, Item 14)
    - Royal Albert Hall, London (120 minutes), 1973 October 10; Audio cassette tape (Box 104, Item 1)
    - Italian Album; Round Records Side 1; Tape #7856 (17 minutes), 1974 May 5; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 104, Item 2)
    - Italian Album; Round Records Side 2; Tape #7857 (20 minutes), 1974 May 5; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 104, Item 3)
    - 1974 Cast Album, Side 1 (22 minutes), Audio tape reel to reel (Box 104, Item 4)
    - Super Bowl X Half Time show including announcer intro (15 minutes), 1976; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 104, Item 5)
    - 76-77 Show Album Side 1, 15ips, 2-track (23 minutes), 1976-1977; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 104, Item 6)
    - 76-77 Show Album Side 2, 15ips, 2-track (20 minutes), 1976-1977; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 104, Item 7)
    - Foreign TV tracks (41 minutes), 1977 January 27; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 104, Item 8)
    - Tucson Symphony 1st half, Tape 1 (57 minutes), 1978 January 29; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 104, Item 9)
    - Tucson Symphony 2 sides (55 minutes), 1978 January; Audio tape to tape (Box 104, Item 10)
    - Super Bowl Master Demo (13 minutes), 1979 July 12; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 105, Item 1)
    - Tom Sullivan three “Childhood” mixes (13 minutes), 1979; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 105, Item 2)
    - Spanish Album Master Side 1 (22 minutes), 1979-1980; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 105, Item 3)
    - Spanish Album Master Side 2 (21 minutes), 1979-1980; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 105, Item 4)
    - NFL Super Bowl National Anthem (6 minutes), 1980 January 12; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 105, Item 5)
    - NFL Super Bowl half time music (15 minutes), 1980 January 14; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 105, Item 6)
    - Super Bowl XIV halftime, studio mix (14 minutes), 1980 January 30; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 105, Item 7)
    - Super Bowl XIV halftime, studio mix stereo (14 minutes), 1980 January 30; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 105, Item 8)
    - Holiday Album Side 1, Album #UWP-1127A (17 minutes), 1980 July; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 105, Item 9)
    - Holiday Album Side 2, Album #UWP-1127B (18 minutes), 1980 July; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 105, Item 10)
    - Spanish album Side 1; Dolby A not decoded during migration, Dolby tone at tail (20 minutes), 1980 August 9; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 105, Item 11)
    - Spanish album Side 2; Dolby A not decoded during migration (19 minutes), 1980 August 9; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 105, Item 12)
    - Album #1131 Spanish, Side 1, Stereo Dolby A, Tones at tail (18 minutes), 1980 October 24; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 105, Item 13)
    - Belgian Symphony Brussels, ¼-track, 2-channels, 2 sides (152 minutes), 1980 November 19; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 106, Item 1)
    - Belgian Symphony Brussels, ¼-track, 2-channels, 2 sides (140 minutes), 1980 November 20; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 106, Item 2)
    - Tucson Symphony Cast C (18 minutes), 1980; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 106, Item 3)
    - Tucson Symphony Cast C, Roll 2 (34 minutes), 1980; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 106, Item 4)
    - NFL Half Time program Super Bowl XIV, studer mix (15 minutes), 1980; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 106, Item 5)
    - Cara 2/B Side B=1132, 1981-1982; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 106, Item 6)
    - Super Bowl XVI, master stadium A with Phyllis (4 tracks combined onto CD disc as 2 channel stereo) (24 minutes), 1982; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 106, Item 7)
    - Super Bowl XVI #1137A Side 1 (15 minutes), 1982; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 106, Item 8)
    - Super Bowl XVI, 4 track halftime playback tape (28 minutes), 1982 January 6; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 106, Item 9)
    - Special Olympics opening playback (19 minutes), 1983 July 6; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 106, Item 10)
    - National Symphony Kennedy Center, complete reel (1st night?) (120 minutes), 1983 August 27; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 106, Item 11)
    - National Symphony Kennedy Center, complete reel (2nd night?) (120 minutes), 1983 August 27; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 106, Item 12)
    - UWP 83-84 #1140A Side 1 (23 minutes), 1983-1984; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 107, Item 1)
    - UWP 83-84 #1140B Side 2 (22 minutes), 1983-1984; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 107, Item 2)
    - More than the Music with News Documentary & St. Peters Square (16 minutes), 1984 April 19; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 107, Item 3)
    - More than the Music Narration Board of Directors Narration (11 minutes), 1984 April 23; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 107, Item 4)
    - Audience w/Pope John Paul II Roll #1 (38 minutes), 1984 May 11; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 107, Item 5)
    - Audience w/Pope John Paul II Roll #2 (36 minutes), 1984 May 11; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 107, Item 6)
    - Audience w/Pope John Paul II Roll #3 (37 minutes), 1984 May 11; Audio tape reel to reel (Box 107, Item 7)